techchee.com 2014-06-17

# Privacy Policy | TechChee.com, gadgets, gizmo and hot tech stuff

## Privacy Policy

At **TechChee.com** , we definitely recognize privacy is important. Here is the information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use or visit **TechChee.com** , and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

_**Email subscription of our newsletter**_  
Your email used for subscription to our newsletter is mainly used for delivering you our newsletter on a daily basis. And occasionally we’ll send you emails for certain announcements or informing you about any gadget/software giveaway contests/sweepstakes, so you can participate and win great prizes. Please note that we’ll never share, sell, or rent your email with anyone without your advanced permission.

_**Log Files**_  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

_**Cookies and Web Beacons**_

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a page that is tailor-made according to your preferences or any features that will be implemented in our website/blog in the future.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies (e.g Google through the Google AdSense program) may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

The followings are the more specific information about Google’s cookie, which may be served by the Google AdSense advertisement on our website, and information on how you can have choices to opt out. 

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and -other sites on the Internet.

\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
